

BERNARD GYUGYI

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP STUDEIS

+421 944 226 733

BUDAPEST, HUNGARY

bernard.gyugyi@gmail.com

PROFILE

As a junior full-stack software developer, I am ready to tackle the upcoming challenges with the skills I learned at a bootcamp and my previous experience as a project manager. I am confident that my passion for software technologies, problem-solving, and creative thinking will keep me on the path of progression. I am excited with collaborating with a team, move forward in my career and solve complex projects.

SKILLS

Languages

Hungarian - native Slovak - native English - fluent

Software Development

Object-Oriented Programming JavaScript, TypeScript, Java Node.is, Express.is, JEST React, CSS, HTML MySQL Git, GitHub, JIRA, SCRUM

EDUCATION

Green Fox Academy

Software Developer (Full-Stack) 2022 - 2023

J. Selye University

Teaching of English and Literature and Informatics 2009 - 2011

Dvory nad Zitavou High School

Mechanic Electrician

EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023 Green Fox Academy - JUNIOR FULL STACK

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Workshop phase (10 weeks): TypeScript, Node.js,

Express, MySQL, DOM, CSS

Project phase (6 weeks): Express.is, GitHub, JavaScript, JIRA, Node.js, Promise/Async/Await,

React, TypeScript, SCSS

Sevenet s.r.o. - Project Manager 2016 - 2022

Project Planning: Defined project scope and created

project schedules

Project Execution: Oversaw project delivery to ensure completion on time, within budget and to customer

satisfaction

Project Closure: Formally closed out projects by conducting reviews and documentation

Maintained regular communication with partner

companies

Managed a technician team in multiple tasks and

provided guidance to meet project objectives

2014 - 2015 Benatti s.r.o. - Sales Representative

> Developing and maintaining relationships with existing and potential customers. Negotiating contracts and closing sales.

Meeting and exceeding sales targets.

2012 - 2015 V2 Music Bar - Bar Manager

Managing the bar staff.

Creating and updating the bar's drink menu and ensuring that all beverages are prepared to the

highest standards.

Maintaining a clean and well-stocked bar area, including restocking supplies and cleaning equipment.

Providing excellent customer service.

Pixmania - Customer Support Specialist 2011 - 2012

Handling incoming customer inquiries via phone, email or chat, providing solutions to customer issues, and escalating complex problems to higher-level

support teams

www.linkedin.com/in/bernardgyugyi